<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>TAS Competition on Home</title><link>https://test.minecrafttas.com/tas-comp/</link><description>Recent content in TAS Competition on Home</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-gb</language><atom:link href="https://test.minecrafttas.com/tas-comp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Rules</title><link>https://test.minecrafttas.com/tas-comp/rules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://test.minecrafttas.com/tas-comp/rules/</guid><description>&lt;ol>
&lt;li>Do &lt;strong>NOT&lt;/strong> talk about your submission, whether it&amp;rsquo;s your time, strats or anything else. Not even a hint that you found the best strat ever.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Do &lt;strong>NOT&lt;/strong> leak the task to non participants, bystanders will discuss new strats that participants can use as an advantage.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>You may resubmit a run within the submission period.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>The submission has to follow the task rules to be valid. Organisers may point out rule breaks so you can resubmit a valid run, but don&amp;rsquo;t always count on that.&lt;br>
Purposefully breaking the rules and submitting it will count as a meme run, check the special rules for that&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Do &lt;strong>NOT&lt;/strong> code your own mods or tools just for this competition. This is not a coding competition and the best tools win.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Working as a team is allowed, but announce all team members when you participate.
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>You are &lt;strong>not&lt;/strong> allowed to play the task in multiplayer on a server&lt;/li>
&lt;li>You are allowed to discuss strats in your team&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Segments from multiple team members stitched together are allowed (e.g. by sharing savestates)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Only one person has to submit the run, but mention all team members in the submission notes&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;p>&lt;em>Rulebreakers&lt;/em> will be disqualified and may re-join once the next round starts. In severe cases this may lead to a ban from the discord.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>