<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tutorials on Home</title><link>https://test.minecrafttas.com/tutorials/</link><description>Recent content in Tutorials on Home</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-gb</language><atom:link href="https://test.minecrafttas.com/tutorials/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Non Playback</title><link>https://test.minecrafttas.com/tutorials/non-playback/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://test.minecrafttas.com/tutorials/non-playback/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="the-basics">The basics&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Instead of choosing each input per frame and play back the TAS at the end, non-playback TASing is the act of screen recording &lt;em>yourself&lt;/em> speedrunning, but setting the game to &lt;em>slow motion&lt;/em>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Later in video editing, you &lt;em>speed up&lt;/em> the footage from slow motion to normal speed.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The result is a video in normal speed, but the player has better reaction times.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Additionally you may use &lt;strong>savestates&lt;/strong>, which is the ability to create a restore point at any time during your run and if you fail at something, you can reload the savestate to try again.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Playback</title><link>https://test.minecrafttas.com/tutorials/playback/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://test.minecrafttas.com/tutorials/playback/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="what-are-pb-tases">What are playback TASes?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Most TASes that you will see are made using some form of playback using an &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Emulator" target=_blank>emulator&lt;/a> with an option called movie playback which allows you to directly playback your TASes in &lt;em>real time&lt;/em>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Playback of these movies require no external tampering (e.g hacks/cheats), to run properly as it is the emulator/console reading a series of inputs from an input file like a &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aseMAEctM1s&amp;amp;t=15s" target=_blank>player piano&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="benefits">What are the benefits of playback TASing?&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="1-ease-of-modification">1. Ease of modification&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Non-playback TASes are unable to modify any inputs in specific sections without having to restart from a savestate. This can be frustrating, especially in places where you can&amp;rsquo;t savestate (Such as in chests or in your inventory). With playback, you can redo specific parts of savestates to refine it however you like through a GUI.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Tools</title><link>https://test.minecrafttas.com/tutorials/tools/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://test.minecrafttas.com/tutorials/tools/</guid><description>&lt;p>Here is a list of commonly used tools in Minecraft TASing&amp;hellip; While you may recognise some of these tools from emulator TASing, the implementation in Minecraft is most likely completely different.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="tickratechanger">Tickratechanger&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This is the name of the module used to slow down or speed up the game speed. As many games, Minecraft runs on a tick based system, which is different to for example SM64, which runs on a frame based system&amp;hellip;&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>